<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ISCKRS</string>
    <string name="kwonyourregis">K/W YOUR REGISTRATION</string>
    <string name="schedule">MY SCHEDULED</string>
    <string name="expadv">.Exploring Recent \nAdvances\u2022</string>
    <string name="invitation">
<![CDATA[
<html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:17px;font-family:ariel;">

<div class="mb-40 pb-20 p-40 bg-gray-lighter pb-50">
        <h4>Dear Friends, </h4>
        <br>
        <p>Greetings from Indian Society of Cornea &amp; Keratorefractive Surgeons!</p>

<p align="justify">It gives us immense pleasure to invite you to the Annual Conference of Indian Society of Cornea &amp; Keratorefractive Surgeons (ISCKRS) that is scheduled to be held from <strong>03rd &amp; 04th August, 2019, Le Meridien, New Delhi</strong>. This Conference will bring together practitioners, researchers and educators from India and abroad who are engaged in state of art academic work in Cornea and Refractive Surgery. The Conference will continue its aim of imparting medical education in the best possible manner in its various sessions. Together with the stallwarts in the field of ophthalmology from across the country and outside, we are planning sessions for Young Ophthalmologists as well.</p>

<p align="justify">The theme of this year's Conference is <strong>"Exploring Recent Advances"</strong>.It will be a two-day event that will involve Live surgery demonstration, Orations &amp; key-note lectures, Sessions on Corneal problems and their solutions, Refractive surgical issues, Video assisted sessions, sessions for Young Ophthalmologists, free paper sessions with awards and hands on wet labs and skill development sessions. </p>

<p align="justify">We look forward to welcome you at the Annual Conference of ISCKRS, Le Meridien, New Delhi.</p>

<p>Yours truly,</p>

<p class="mb-30"><span class="pull-left"><strong>Prof. Jeewan S Titiyal</strong> <br>President, ISCKRS</span>	 <span class="pull-right"><strong>Prof. Rajesh Sinha</strong> <br>Gen. Secretary, ISCKRS</span></p>


        </div>
 </body>
</html>
]]>
</string>
    <string name="highlight">
<![CDATA[
<html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
 <h4>
     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; • Live Surgery Demonstration</br>
     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; • Skill Development Wetlabs</br>
     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; • Video Assisted Courses</br>
     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; • Certification of Trainees</br>
     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; • Yo Sessions</br>
     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; • Interesting Case Presentation</br>
     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; • Clinical Debates</br>
</h4>

</body>
</html>
]]>
</string>

    <string name="rupy"><![CDATA[ <font color=#FCA723>₹</font> ]]></string>
    <string name="doller"><![CDATA[ <font color=#FCA723>US$</font> ]]></string>

    <string name="imp_note">
        <![CDATA[
<html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
<h4>Please read below before proceeding:</h4>
<ul class="ml-20">
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> For Spot Registration: Complete kit will be subject to availability.<br>
    </li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> Photo I-Card will be required at the time of collection of registration kit.<br>
    </li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> **Proof of residency required from HOD along with the registration form.<br>
    </li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> There will be no refund on cancellation of registration.<br>
    </li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> Wearing of identity badge is mandatory at all times.<br>
    </li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> Entry to Scientific Sessions &amp; Exhibition<br>
    </li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> Area will be Restricted to Registered Delegates only.</li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> Lost badge will be replaced at the registration counter for a fee Rs. 200/-.<br>
    </li>
  <li><i class="fa fa-angle-right"></i> Pre-Registration will be closed on 30th June 2019.</li>
</ul>


</body>
</html>

]]></string>

    <array name="img_arr_commiti">
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team1.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team2.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team3.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team4.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team5.jpg</item>


        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team6.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team7.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team8.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team9.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team10.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team11.jpg</item>
        <item>http://isckrs.com/images/team/team12.jpg</item>
    </array>
    <array name="nameimg">
        <item>Dr. Michael Belin#USA</item>
        <item>Dr. Harminder S Dua#UK</item>
        <item>Dr. Jodhbir Mehta#Singapore</item>
        <item>Dr. Tarek Katamish#Egypt</item>
        <item>Dr. Avi Solomon#Bril</item>
        <item>Dr. Ahmad Khalil#Egypt</item>
        <item>Dr. Leonardo Torquetti#Brazil</item>

        <item>Dr. V K Raju#USA</item>
        <item>Dr. Kamran M. Riaz#USA</item>
        <item>Dr. Daya Sharma#Australia</item>
        <item>Dr. Pichit Naripyhaphan#Thailand</item>
        <item>Dr. Hozzam Ziada#Egypt</item>
    </array>
    <array name="namemember">
        <item>Dr. Radhika Tandon</item>
        <item>Dr. Hardeep Singh</item>
        <item>Dr. Alkesh Chaudhary</item>
        <item>Dr. Naginder Vashisht</item>
        <item>Dr. Vinod Kumar</item>
        <item>Dr. Sandhya Makhija</item>
        <item>Dr. Pawan Goyal</item>
        <item>Dr. M C Aggarwal</item>


    </array>
    <array name="representative">
        <item>Dr. Ashu Agarwal</item>
        <item>Dr. Rohit Saxena</item>
    </array>
    <array name="exmember">
        <item>Dr. Kamlesh</item>
        <item>Dr. M. Vanathi</item>
        <item>Dr. Vipul Nayar</item>
    </array>
    <array name="tabname">
        <item>HOME</item>
        <item>REGISTRATION</item>
        <item>FACULTY</item>
        <item>VENUE</item>
        <item>OFFICE BEARERS</item>
        <item>K/W YOUR REGISTRATION</item>
        <item>JOIN ISCKRS</item>
        <item>CONTACT</item>
        <item>NOTIFICATION</item>
        <item>LOGIN</item>
    </array>
    <string name="venue">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head></head>
 <body >
       <h3>About Delhi</h3>
       <div style="text-align:justify">

          New Delhi, the capital of India, is a bustling metropolis that
          has an amazing mix of modernisation and carefully preserved antiquity.
          Sprawled over the west bank of the river Yamuna, it is one of the fastest
          growing cities in India. New Delhi was built by a British architect Edward Lutyens
          in 1912 as the new capital of the British Raj. The Victorian architecture
          now intermingles with the city\'s high rise buildings. Concrete flyovers built
          to ease the growing traffic are interspersed with well laid gardens, Mughal tombs,
          forts and monuments.</br>
          </br>

<font size="4"><h3>Places to Visit in Delhi</h3></font>
Red Fort</br>
Jama Masjid</br>
Chandni Chowk</br>
Swaminarayan Akshardham</br>
Humayun's Tomb</br>
Qutab Minar</br>
India Gate</br>
Lotus Temple</br>
          </div>
    </body>
</html>

]]></string>

    <string name="contact">
         <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
 <div class="col-xs-12 col-sm-4 col-md-10 text-center text-white">
          <h3 class="mb-0 mt-10 font-30 text-white">Indian Society of Cornea &amp;
            Keratorefractive Surgeons </h3>
            <p><em>Furtherance of knowledge of Cornea, Corneal diseases &amp; Kerato-Refractive surgery</em></p>

            <ul class="list-inline text-center mb-5">
            <li class="m-0 pl-10 pr-10"> <i class="fa fa-phone"></i> <a class="text-black" href="#">+91-9650688803, +91-9650268007</a> </li>
            <li class="m-0 pl-10 pr-10"> <i class="fa fa-envelope-o"></i> <a class="text-black" href="#">isckrs@gmail.com</a> </li>
          </ul>
        </div>
    </body>
</html>

]]>

    </string>
    <string name="tour_1">
          <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head><style>img{max-width: 100%; width:auto; height: auto;}</style></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
 <div class="text">
<p><img border="1" src="http://doscon18.org/images/1.jpg" height="300" width="300" ></p><p><strong>Lotus  Temple</strong> - It is the  Bahai house of worship and a fairly recent construction and is largely admired  for its architecture.</p>
<p><strong>Qutub  Minar</strong> - The Minar  (tower) was built in the year 1212 A.D and stands at a height of 72.5 mtrs in  the courtyard of the Quwwat-ul-Islam masjid. This is the oldest historical  monument in Delhi and is a must see for any visitor to this city.</p>
<p><strong>Humayun\'s  Tomb</strong> - Humayun\'s tomb  is believed to have been designed by his widow. Its plan, based on the  description of Islamic paradise gardens, is known to have inspired the TajMahal  and many later Mughal tombs.</p>
<p><strong>Shopping </strong> - Sarojini Nagar &amp; Delhi  Haat - Sarojini Nagar  Market is very popular among the Delhi citizens because of having great bargaining  here in every product such as home furnishing, fashionable clothing, bags,  cosmetics, belts, sweaters, footwear,
 and other accessories. This market is a  favorite place for the students, tourists and
 college goings due to great  bargaining at this place <strong>Delhi Haat</strong>–It  provides the ambience of a traditional Rural Haat or village market, but one  suited for more contemporary needs. Here one sees a synthesis of crafts,  food and cultural activity.</p>
 </div>

 <div>
<h5>For any query or booking please contact</h5>
Ms. Shivani Srivastav</br>
Mobile: 9654800674</br>
Email: shivani.srivastav@icegroupindia.com
 </div>
    </body>
</html>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tour_2">
          <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head><style>img{max-width: 100%; width:auto; height: auto;}</style></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
<div class="content">



                                                    <div class="text">
                                                    <p><img border="1" src="http://doscon18.org/images/2.jpg" height="300" width="400"></p>
                                                    <p><strong>Red  Fort</strong> - A fascinating  building, built with red sandstones is an example of the rich Mughal  architecture. Red Fort is a venue to the Independence Day parade of India.</p>

<p><strong>Jama  Masjid </strong>- Is the biggest  masjid in India, built by Shahjahan in 1650 A.D.</p>
<p><strong>President  House</strong> - Situated on  Raisina Hill this was built to be the official residence of the Viceroy, and  later became the official residence of the President of India</p>
<p><strong>India  Gate </strong>- Originally  known as the All India War Memorial, built in the memory of the 90,000 Indian soldiers  killed in the First World War, is a freestanding arch with a height of 42.5  mtrs, designed and built by Edwin Lutyens in 1931.</p>
<p><strong>Parliament  House</strong> -This is a huge  circular, colonnaded building where the Indian parliament meets.</p>
<p><strong>Shopping - </strong>Sarojini Nagar &amp; Delhi  Haat - Sarojini Nagar  Market is very popular among the Delhi citizens because of having great bargaining  here in every product such as home furnishing, fashionable clothing, bags,  cosmetics, belts, sweaters, footwear, and other accessories. This market is a  favorite place for the students, tourists and college goings due to great  bargaining at this place. <strong>Delhi Haat</strong> – It provides the ambience of a traditional Rural Haat or village market, but  one suited for more contemporary needs. Here one sees a synthesis of  crafts, food and cultural activity.</p></div>
                                                </div>
                                                 <div>
<h5>For any query or booking please contact</h5>
Ms. Shivani Srivastav</br>
Mobile: 9654800674</br>
Email: shivani.srivastav@icegroupindia.com
 </div>
    </body>
</html>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tour_3">
          <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head><style>img{max-width: 100%; width:auto; height: auto;}</style></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
<div class="content">


                                                    <div class="text">

                                                    <p><img border="1" src="http://doscon18.org/images/3.jpg" height="300" width="400"></p>
                                                    <p>Jaipur, known as the "<strong>Pink City</strong>", is the capital of the colourful state of Rajasthan. It has the distinction of being a well planned and laid out city. As you drive through the old part of town, you will witness a life most unlike others. Witness how the city blooms during the day in a kaleidoscope of color and sound. The capital of Rajasthan, Jaipur is not only the gateway to the state; it was laid out by Maharaja Sawai Jai Singh II of the Kachchawaha dynasty from Amber. In Jaipur, visit the magnificent Amber Fort, City Palace, Museum, The Observatory etc. Enjoy the elephant ride at Amber Fort</p></div>
                                                </div>
                                                 <div>
<h5>For any query or booking please contact</h5>
Ms. Shivani Srivastav</br>
Mobile: 9654800674</br>
Email: shivani.srivastav@icegroupindia.com
 </div>
    </body>
</html>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tour_4">
          <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head><style>img{max-width: 100%; width:auto; height: auto;}</style></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
<div class="content">


                                                    <div class="text">
                                                   <p><img border="1" src="http://doscon18.org/images/4.jpg" height="300" width="400"></p>
                                                    <p><strong> Golden Triangle</strong> tour is one of the most popular tourist circuits of India. This tour presents a true color of India with Delhi, a rich tapestry of contrasts that is characteristic of this complex land, Agra, the zenith of art &amp;an enshrined romance and Jaipur - exuberant with color for enjoying North India\'s fascinating cultural heritage. The combination of all the three cities presents the potpourri of India.</p></div>
                                                </div>
                                                 <div>
<h5>For any query or booking please contact</h5>
Ms. Shivani Srivastav</br>
Mobile: 9654800674</br>
Email: shivani.srivastav@icegroupindia.com
 </div>
    </body>
</html>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tour_5">
          <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head><style>img{max-width: 100%; width:auto; height: auto;}</style></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
<div class="content">


                                                    <div class="text">
                                                  <p><img border="1" src="http://doscon18.org/images/5.jpg" height="300" width="400"></p>
                                                    <p><strong>Vrindavan and Mathura</strong> are the most important places of pilgrimage for devotees of Krishna. Krishna was born in Mathura and spent his childhood in Vrindavan. A long line of picturesque ghats - with their steps leading to the water\'s edge, arched gateways and temple spires extending along the right bank of the River Yamuna, emphasize the sacred character of the town of Mathura. Vrindavan today, is noted for its numerous temples.</p>
 </div>
                                                </div>
                                                 <div>
<h5>For any query or booking please contact</h5>
Ms. Shivani Srivastav</br>
Mobile: 9654800674</br>
Email: shivani.srivastav@icegroupindia.com
 </div>
    </body>
</html>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tour_6">
          <![CDATA[
        <html>
 <head><style>img{max-width: 100%; width:auto; height: auto;}</style></head>
 <body style="color:black;font-size:16px;font-family:ariel;">
<div class="content">


                                                    <div class="text">
                                                    <p><img border="1" src="http://doscon18.org/images/6.jpg" height="300" width="400"></p>
                                                    <p> Agra is globally renowned as the city of the Taj Mahal, visit the monument of love and imagination that represents India to the world. It is a town that lives mainly in the past. </p>

 <p>The Taj Mahal is an ivory-white marble mausoleum on the south bank of the Yamuna river in the Indian city of Agra. The Taj Mahal was commissioned by Shah Jahan in 1631, to be built in the memory of his wife Mumtaz Mahal, a Persian princess who died giving birth to their 14th child, Gauhara Begum. Construction of the Taj Mahal began in 1632. The imperial court documenting Shah Jahan\'s grief after the death of Mumtaz Mahal illustrate the love story held as the inspiration for Taj Mahal. </p>
  <p>
<h5>For any query or booking please contact</h5>
Ms. Shivani Srivastav</br>
Mobile: 9654800674</br>
Email: shivani.srivastav@icegroupindia.com
 </p>
 </div>
                                                </div>

    </body>
</html>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="hint_uname">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Mobile</string>
    <string name="conference_venue"><h2 class="text-uppercase">Conference Venue</h2></string>
</resources>
